<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Gear Up And Go (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.GearUpAndGo</packageId>
  <author>Uuugggg</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/GearUpAndGo</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.0</li>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/WAEzk68.png[/img]
Update of Uuuggggs mod
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1316142788

[img]https://i.imgur.com/7Gzt3Rg.png[/img]

[table]
    [tr]
        [td][url=https://invite.gg/Mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td]
        [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/GearUpAndGo][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/NOW7jU1.png[/img]
Adds a button to draft, swap gear, then go to the target location

---

"A Raid! Is it time for battle!"

"Suit up!"

"Okay I've got my armor vest, I'm going to go plant some corn"

"I've already got armor so I'm still mining"

"GET OVER HERE NOW"

"But I haven't got my helmet on yet"

---

Gearing up for battle is a mess. This mod makes sense out of it.

Normally (if you don't just wear cumbersome armor 24/7) to equip everyone with new gear, you need to change all their outfits, draft/undraft them so they stop their job, they find new gear, then they continue work. You want them to go to the defensive lines, but you have to catch each one as they finish gearing up. So, this mod makes that whole process a single button.

---

A button to Gear Up And Go somewhere. Just Click the "Gear &amp; Go" button and target a spot: Colonists gear up for their outfit, draft, then go there. 

Clicking the button will set a policy from the mod [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1541460369]Better Pawn Control[/url]. Set the policy name in the Settings. 
- You can right-click the icon to choose the policy for that click
- You can alt-click the Gear+Go target to not set the policy, just gear+go
- See https://youtu.be/UiuQuQP7uFg for exact how-to.

It remembers the previous policy, and shift-clicking the button (when green) resets the policy. (Shift-clicking no longer undrafts - I didn't find that to be best) There's also an alert icon onscreen to remind you the better pawn control policy was set, click that to reset as well.

If you don't use Better Pawn Control... well. Go use that. But if not, you'll need to manually set the outfits for pawns before clicking the button.

---

Combat Extended Support - it will look for changes in the loadout as well. BCP will set the policy, Gear+Go uses the set loadout to find things to grab.

Though I found it didn't always work with heavy things - the limit was reached, but trying again sometimes worked. So I'm gonna blame CE for having such low weight capacity.

---

No special decisions are added here. Colonists simply change apparel as normal, then when nothing is needed to wear, they are drafted and ordered to a spot.


---

Re: [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=761219125]Defensive Positions[/url]

Gear Up and Go To Defensive Positions would be cool, but Gear+Go targeting the Defensive Positions widget would require a certain amount of collaboration between two mods.

Instead, you can Gear+Go to a spot as normal, then shift-click Defensive Positions to queue it up (possibly another key, check settings, but in either case that's just queueing the Defensive Positions like normal)


--- 

Source on github: https://github.com/alextd/Rimworld-GearUpAndGo
Ludeon Forum Thread: https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=39320.0
People seem to like donating so why not: [b]https://ko-fi.com/alextd[/b]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/Rs6T6cr.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[/list]
</description>
</ModMetaData>

